question_data = [
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "question": "In the video game &quot;Splatoon&quot;, the playable characters were originally going to be rabbits instead of squids.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Animals",
      "question": "Kangaroos keep food in their pouches next to their children.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
      "question": "Water always boils at 100&deg;C, 212&deg;F, 373.15K, no matter where you are.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "question": "Pac-Man was invented by the designer Toru Iwatani while he was eating pizza.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Science: Gadgets",
      "question": "Microphones can be used not only to pick up sound, but also to project sound similar to a speaker.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Musicals &amp; Theatres",
      "question": "IMAX stands for Image Maximum.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "question": "In &quot;Super Mario 64&quot;, collecting 100 coins on a level will give you a 1-UP.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Film",
      "question": "The film &quot;2001: A Space Odyssey&quot; was released on December 31st, 2000.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Tokyo is the capital of Japan.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "question": "&quot;Resident Evil 7&quot; is the first first-person Resident Evil game.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    }
  
]